<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolios on Collin Sherman, Computer Science student at Washington and Lee University</title>
    <link>https://collinsherman.github.io/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portfolios on Collin Sherman, Computer Science student at Washington and Lee University</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://collinsherman.github.io/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Calculator App</title>
      <link>https://collinsherman.github.io/portfolio/calculator-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collinsherman.github.io/portfolio/calculator-app/</guid>
      <description>This project was my first GUI app that I created, all the way back in my Fundamentals of Programming II class. We were tasked with creating a copy of the iOS calculator and were graded on functionality as well as aestic similarities. I earned a 95&amp;frasl;100 on the assignment, receiving full marks for aestetics, but being docked five points for my clear method not working completely correct. Nonetheless, this was a cool project because I got to see the my own hard work come to fruition in an app that I could actually use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software Development Projects</title>
      <link>https://collinsherman.github.io/portfolio/software-dev-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collinsherman.github.io/portfolio/software-dev-projects/</guid>
      <description>These were fun projects because they was my first true collaborative project. My team of four students, including myself, were put together and tasked with developing these two apps, with only a little bit of starter code from our professor. I was the Git Repo Manager and focused on the display side of the projects, though we all worked on the backend coding to varying degrees.
The War app (pictured above) was a challenge at first, as we could not get our two &amp;ldquo;player&amp;rdquo; objects to work correctly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sprint Generator</title>
      <link>https://collinsherman.github.io/portfolio/sprint-generator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collinsherman.github.io/portfolio/sprint-generator/</guid>
      <description>This project is a particular source of pride for myself because of its practicality and usefulness.
As a running back, running sprints are particularly important in my training. But, running the same set distances over and over is not only boring, but also not exactly the best training, as during a play I could run anywhere from five to 100 yards (I don&amp;rsquo;t train to get tackled for a loss). So, in order to attempt to simulate the randomness of the game of football, the idea of the Sprint Generator came into mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer 2017 Internship</title>
      <link>https://collinsherman.github.io/portfolio/summer-2017-internship/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collinsherman.github.io/portfolio/summer-2017-internship/</guid>
      <description>My focus over this internship was centered around the development of static sites, along with some additional applications that I built.
I worked for Sherman Digital LLC, headed by my older brother. Though this was odd at first, having my brother as a boss, we were able to get past this and have a professional relationship while on the job. I learned a lot and was able to produce some products that impressed myself especially.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theory of Computation</title>
      <link>https://collinsherman.github.io/portfolio/theory-of-computation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://collinsherman.github.io/portfolio/theory-of-computation/</guid>
      <description>In my Theory of Computation class, we were tasked with finding out if a Context Free Language was decidable or not. To do this, we were to use an algorithm from our textbook that wasn&amp;rsquo;t the easiest to look at, to say the least. I kept getting tripped up along the way for one reason or another, so out of frustration, I decided to write a program that would follow the algorithm and print out the answer for me.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>